>> I'M JOSE CANSECO,
6-TIME ALL STAR, MVP.
JOES, YOU HAVE NO CHANCE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE STAYED HOME.
>> I'M RANDY "THE NATURAL"
COUTURE, 4-TIME ULTIMATE
FIGHTING CHAMPION.
JOES, YOU'RE GONNA BE LUCKY
TO WALK OUT OF THAT OCTAGON.
>> I'M KEVIN WILLIS.
I PLAYED 21 NBA SEASONS.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT STEPPING
IN THE PAINT WITH ME.
>> I AM MICHAEL IRVIN,
"THE PLAYMAKER," 3-TIME
SUPER BOWL CHAMPION.
HEY, JOE, I AM LIKE DEATH.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU PREPARE,
WHEN I HIT, YOU ARE NOT READY.
YEAH.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH, IT'S ME.
>> HA HA HA!
>> YOU DON'T BELONG IN HERE
'CAUSE YOU'RE WAY TOO
WELL-DRESSED.
>> I DON'T WANT NO MESSING
AROUND NOW.
WE CANNOT LOSE.
WE WILL NOT LOSE.
NO JOKE.
AND I'M SERIOUS NOW.
I HOPE THEY DON'T THINK THEY CAN
GO COME UP AND LINE UP ON ME.
I WILL MAKE YOU FEEL THE SAME
PAIN THOSE PROS FELT IN THE NFL.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU, I'M
DOING IT.
>> THEY ARE LEGENDS OF THE GAME,
BATTLE-TESTED IN ARENAS
AND STADIUMS BEFORE MILLIONS
OF SCREAMING FANS.
>> COME ON!
>> THEY LIVED WHAT FEW HAVE
DREAMED AND YOU WATCHED THEM
DO IT, WONDERING WHAT IT MUST
HAVE BEEN LIKE TO COMPETE
AGAINST THE BEST.
NOW REGULAR JOES GET THE CHANCE
TO SEE HOW THEY MEASURE UP
AGAINST THE PROS IN A
COMPETITION WHERE ANYTHING CAN
HAPPEN.
>> IT'S HELL IN THE HOLE!
>> REAL SPORTS, REAL PROS,
NO MERCY.
THIS IS "PROS VS. JOES."
THREE JOES WILL ENTER, BUT ONLY
ONE IS GONNA LEAVE.
WHAT'S CRACKIN', EVERYBODY?
I'M PETROS PAPADAKIS,
AND THIS IS "PROS VS. JOES."
TONIGHT IN THE HOME DEPOT
CENTER, THESE 3 REGULAR JOES
WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO COMPETE
AGAINST SOME OF THE GREATEST
ATHLETES PROFESSIONAL SPORTS
HAVE TO OFFER.
LET'S MEET THE PROS.
HE NEVER MET A BALL HE COULDN'T
DESTROY.
THE ORIGINAL BASH BROTHER,
JOSE CANSECO.
>> HOW YOU DOING, VICTIMS?
I MIGHT HAVE TO HIT LEFT-HANDED
AGAINST YOU GUYS.
YOU LOOK SO PITIFUL.
>> THE FIRST MAN EVER TO WIN A
UFC TITLE IN TWO DIFFERENT
WEIGHT CLASSES, RANDY COUTURE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I'D LIKE TO WELCOME
THE NEWEST MEMBERS TO THE QUICK
TAP CLUB.
>> HEH!
>> HE'S RACKED UP OVER 16,000
POINTS AND 11,000 REBOUNDS
IN HIS NBA CAREER.
KEVIN WILLIS.
>> IT'S HELL IN THE HOLE,
YOUNG FELLA.
REMEMBER THAT.
>> GAME TIME, BABY, GAME TIME.
>> OUR FINAL PRO IS JUST
A 5-TIME PRO-BOWLER, SUPER BOWL
CHAMPION, TRULY ONE OF THE
GREATEST WIDE RECEIVERS EVER TO
PLAY THE GAME, "THE PLAYMAKER"--
MICHAEL IRVIN.
>> WE WILL HAVE FUN...
BUT I WILL WIN.
>> AS MUCH AS YOU JOES WANT TO
SUCCEED, THESE PROS ARE HERE
TO STOP YOU.
SO LET'S MEET YOU JOES.
JOE NUMBER 3, GIVE ME
YOUR STATS.
>> AARON McKEEVER.
I'M FROM OMAHA, NEBRASKA.
I'M 6'2", 205.
I GOT IT AND I'M GONNA BRING IT.
>> WHERE YOU BRINGIN' IT TO?
>> I GUESS WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT.
>> JOE NUMBER 2?
>> I'M JAY McKEOWN, 28, 6'2",
220 OF PURE ATHLETE.
>> YOU OFTEN SAY PROFESSIONAL
ATHLETES ARE ALL WHINY
AND OVERPAID.
I MEAN, DO YOU STILL FEEL
THAT WAY?
>> YOU KNOW, THERE'S A FEW
OF THEM HERE TODAY THAT ARE,
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO SEE
WHAT WE CAN DO ABOUT THAT.
>> JOE NUMBER ONE, GIVE ME
YOUR STATS.
>> DAWAN OWENS, 6'4", 225,
ORIGINALLY FROM BALTIMORE,
MARYLAND.
>> NOW, YOU DO SOME STAND-UP
COMEDY.
ANYTHING FUNNY
ABOUT THESE 4 GUYS?
>> JOSE, COME ON.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> CAN'T DO NOTHING WITH THESE
TODAY.
COME ON, BABY, YOU CAN'T.
NONE OF THAT TODAY.
>> IT'S OK.
I'M GONNA MAKE IT UP ON YOU NOW.
>> BRING IT, BABY.
>> ALL RIGHT, BOYS.
THIS IS HOW IT'S GONNA WORK.
YOU 3 JOES ARE GONNA COMPETE
AGAINST THESE 4 PROS IN 3
MATCH-UPS.
WHOEVER WINS THE MOST MATCH-UPS
IS GOING ON TO OVERTIME.
THAT'LL BE TWO OF YOU.
IN OVERTIME, YOU WILL FACE
ALL 4 PROS IN THEIR OWN SPORT.
WHOEVER WINS OVERTIME NOT ONLY
WINS BRAGGING RIGHTS FOR LIFE,
BUT YOU GET TO TAKE THE JERSEY
OFF THE PRO'S BACK.
NOW, MORE IMPORTANTLY, YOU
QUALIFY FOR OUR CHAMPIONSHIP
SHOW.
WHEN YOU WIN THE CHAMPIONSHIP,
YOU WIN A NEW TOYOTA TUNDRA,
TICKETS AND AIRFARE AND HOTEL TO
THE WORLD SERIES, THE FINAL
FOUR, THE BCS CHAMPIONSHIP, AND
THE BIGGEST GAME EVERY YEAR IN
PRO FOOTBALL, AND LET ME TELL
YOU, THAT IS A SUPER, SUPER
PRIZE.
YOU GUYS READY TO ROCK 'N' ROLL?
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> FIRST THINGS FIRST.
YOU'RE GONNA DO WHAT A LOT OF
NFL DBs COULDN'T DO FOR YEARS,
AND THAT'S GUARD MICHAEL IRVIN.
>> THIS IS THE REAL THING.
>> HEAD TO THE LOCKER ROOM.
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE THESE [BLEEP]
GUYS?
TO THINK THEY EVEN HAVE A CHANCE
AGAINST US.
>> MAN, I DON'T BELIEVE THEY'RE
TALKING TO ME LIKE THAT.
>> REALLY COCKY, AREN'T THEY?
>> TELL YOU WHAT, THOUGH...
THAT COMEDIAN GUY, MAKING
ALL THOSE LITTLE JOKES?
SERIOUSLY.
AND HE THINKS IT'S A JOKE,
MAN.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
I SAID, "I JUST WANT TO CATCH
THAT FIRST BALL AND RUN RIGHT
AT HIM, SEE HOW MUCH WE CAN
CRACK HIM UP."
>> WE GOT TO GET EACH AND EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF THEM SOMEHOW AND
JUST TEACH THEM WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE A PRO FOR REAL.
>> LET'S WATCH SOME TAPE
OF THESE GUYS.
>> LET'S WATCH SOME TAPE.
>> GAME TIME NOW.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M TALKING [BLEEP] OUT THERE,
TOO, TO ALL OF THEM,
BUT RANDY COUTURE?
I AIN'T EVEN MESSING WITH RANDY.
>> OH, HE'S A BAD DUDE.
>> WHAT TEAM DOES MICHAEL IRVIN
PLAY FOR?
COWGIRLS OR THE--
>> YEAH, HE WAS A CHEERLEADER.
>> CHEERLEADER, YEAH.
HE'S THE HEAD CHEERLEADER.
THAT'S CRAZY.
>> HI, I'M JAY McKEOWN.
I'M FROM SOUTHERN MARYLAND,
LA PLATA, MARYLAND.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN A PRO.
ANYBODY YOU CAN THINK OF,
I COULD COMPETE WITH THEM
RIGHT THIS SECOND IN ANY SPORT.
>> THAT GUY'S A VICTIM FOR SURE.
>> YEAH, BIG TIME.
>> THIS IS WHAT I'VE BEEN DOING
FOR THE PAST 7 YEARS OF MY LIFE.
NOT ONLY AN ATHLETE,
BUT A SOLDIER, TOO.
MIKE, MAN, IT'S YOUR TIME
TO COME GET SOME, BABY.
>> HE'S WEARING A REDSKIN SHIRT.
I ALWAYS BEAT THE REDSKINS,
SO THAT'S EASY.
>> WHOO!
>> MAN, WHAT IS THAT,
AN 8-FOOT BASKET?
>> NO, 6-FOOT, ACTUALLY.
>> YEAH, WHAT WAS THAT?
>> ALL I WANT TO KNOW IS, ARE
THE PROS READY TO GO AGAINST ME?
>> LOOK AT THAT.
NASTY JUMP SHOT.
>> BASEBALL, BASKETBALL,
FOOTBALL.
AM I GOOD AT EVERYTHING?
PRETTY MUCH, YEAH.
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE GOOD
AT LOSING AND CRYING.
>> COME ON!
JUKE STYLE, BABY!
COME ON, COME ON!
UP, DOWN, UP!
>> WHAT IS HE DOING, MAN?
THAT'S NOT BASKETBALL.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> HE'S LOST HIS MIND, POOR GUY.
>> YEAH, HE IS WORN OUT.
>> MY NAME IS AARON McKEEVER,
AND I'M COMING TO [BLEEP]
YOU GUYS UP.
>> THIS IS GOOD.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT HACK!
THAT'S A SOFTBALL SWING.
>> YOU GUYS ARE WEAK, WASHED UP,
LOST YOUR STEP.
I'M 34 YEARS OLD
AND I'VE GOT IT.
I GOT THE STRENGTH.
THIS [BLEEP] TOO EASY.
YOU GUYS BETTER BE SCARED
BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GO
BACK HOME TO YOUR FAMILY AFTER
YOU GOT WHUPPED BY THIS JOE.
>> THEY'RE A BUST.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE LOOK
ON THEIR FACE WHEN THEY CLOSE
THAT CAGE DOOR.
>> OH.
>> I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE EASY,
BUT IT'S GONNA BE EASIER.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE EVEN
CONSIDERING EVEN STEPPING TO US.
I--I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> ONE MAN AGAINST 3.
BEEN LIKE THAT ALL MY LIFE.
>> ALL RIGHT, JOES.
THERE HE IS, THE PLAYMAKER.
MATCH-UP ONE IS VERY SIMPLE.
YOU'RE GONNA GO ONE-ON-ONE
WITH MICHAEL IRVIN.
THE FIRST JOE TO STOP MICHAEL
TWO TIMES IS GOING TO TAKE
MATCH-UP ONE.
>> Y'ALL GOT TOO MUCH STUFF ON.
GOT ON TOO MUCH STUFF, HOMES.
I'M TALKING ABOUT ALL THE PANTS
YOU GOT ON.
THAT'S WHAT CHUMPS WEAR.
>> DAWAN OWENS, YOU'RE FIRST,
MAN.
JOE NUMBER ONE.
SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
MICHAEL IRVIN'S ONLY GOT 11,904
YARDS IN HIS CAREER, BUT MAYBE
OLD AGE AND 3 OF THOSE SUPER
BOWL RINGS WILL WEIGH HIM DOWN.
>> LET'S GO AND SET THE TONE.
>> MICHAEL IRVIN WITH A GOOD
BURST OFF THE LINE.
THAT IS A GO ROUTE
AND THAT IS SEPARATION
AND THAT IS A TOUCHDOWN
FOR MICHAEL IRVIN.
>> OH, MY!
>> OH, COME ON, DAWG.
DAWG, YOU GOT TO DO BETTER
THAN THAT.
YOU'RE OUT THERE--LITTLE LEAGUE
OUT HERE.
I'M 40 YEARS OLD.
>> NICE WORK, MIKE.
>> NEXT UP, JOE NUMBER 3,
AARON McKEEVER.
>> IF YOU NEED ME, MAN, I'LL
COME OUT THERE AND HIT HIM
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
>> NO, I GOT HIM.
>> PLAYMAKER, LOOKING LIKE HE'S
STILL GOT ALL THOSE MOVES.
IRVIN COMES OFF THE LINE HARD,
CUTS TO THE INSIDE.
IRVIN WITH THE CATCH.
OH, AND HE'S DOING McKEEVER.
McKEEVER TRIPPING OVER HIS FEET.
IRVIN INTO THE END ZONE.
OH, AND THAT'S A TOUCHDOWN,
BUT McKEEVER WITH A LATE HIT
ON THE PLAYMAKER!
>> TOUCHDOWN.
>> AND MICHAEL IRVIN IS TAUNTING
AARON McKEEVER.
THAT IS REALLY RUBBING IT IN!
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THAT AGAIN.
IRVIN MAKES A GREAT MOVE IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE FIELD, CUTS
BACK, THEN HEADED FOR THE PYLON.
HE TAUNTS McKEEVER, WHO TAKES
HIM DOWN WITH A LATE HIT.
>> I THOUGHT HE WAS AT THE ONE.
>> I DIDN'T REALLY WANT TO GO
IN THE END ZONE.
I SPENT TOO MUCH TIME IN THERE
ALREADY.
I JUST PUT THE BALL IN
LIKE THIS.
YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING?
I SPENT HALF OF MY LIFE
IN THE END ZONE.
I THOUGHT JUST TO GIVE THE BALL
A TRIP.
THAT'S ALL I WANTED TO DO.
[PROS LAUGHING]
>> COMING UP
ON "PROS VS. JOES"...
TOUCHDOWN FOR MICHAEL IRVIN.
>> YO, JERRY JONES IS GONNA
CALL ME AFTER HE SEES THIS.
>> HERE COMES COUTURE.
COUTURE'S AFTER HIM AGAIN.
THAT'S THE OLD FIGURE-4
LEG LOCK.
>> WELCOME BACK
TO "PROS VS. JOES."
WE'RE HERE IN MATCH-UP ONE,
WHERE MICHAEL IRVIN HAS SCHOOLED
THE FIRST TWO JOES ON THE
GRIDIRON.
THEY HAVEN'T STOPPED HIM
FROM SCORING TWO TIMES TO WIN
THE MATCH-UP.
NEXT UP, JAY McKEOWN.
EVERYTHING STRAPPED ON TIGHT?
>> READY TO ROCK, MAN.
>> ALL RIGHT, GET OUT THERE
AND GO SEE THE PLAYMAKER.
FIRST DOWN FOR JAY McKEOWN.
GOT THE HAMMIES STRAPPED UP
LIKE A POP WARNER PLAYER.
>> HEY, NOW--HEY, YOU KNOW?
BEEN A WHILE SINCE I DID THIS.
I FEEL GOOD DOING THIS, TOO--
HOMEBOY, HOMEBOY.
HOMEBOY, LOOK OVER HERE.
HERE'S WHERE YOUR PROBLEM LIE.
>> REDSKINS, BABY.
REDSKINS, BABY.
COME ON.
COME ON, COWBOY.
>> AND THERE IS SOME TALKING
GOING ON.
>> HUT!
>> THIS IS JAY'S FIRST ATTEMPT
AT STOPPING MICHAEL IRVIN.
OH, AND THAT BALL IS OVERTHROWN.
>> HE HAD HIM WORKED TO DEATH.
>> MICHAEL DID BEAT JAY McKEOWN.
>> YOU GOT ME TURNED AROUND.
GOOD CATCH, MAN.
>> BUT DID NOT SCORE
A TOUCHDOWN.
JAY McKEOWN IS NOW OUR LEADER.
>> WHOO!
GOT ME TURNED AROUND!
GOOD LORD.
>> SO AFTER FIRST DOWN,
JAY McKEOWN IS OUR LEADER
WITH ONE STOP.
HE NOW NEEDS ONLY ONE MORE STOP
TO WIN THE MATCH-UP.
>> LET'S GO.
LET'S KEEP GOING.
WHAT ARE WE RESTING FOR?
>> GETTING READY
FOR SECOND DOWN.
>> LET'S GO.
>> JOES, DAWG.
>> I KNOW.
>> NOTHING! ZERO!
ZILCH. LOOK AT HIM.
>> DAWAN OWENS IS UP AGAIN.
HE NEEDS A STOP TO TIE JAY.
>> NO REDEMPTION HERE, BABY.
>> HUT!
>> COMING ACROSS, AND HE PULLS
HIM IN, TRYING TO TAKE HIM BACK
TO THE CORNER.
THE BALL IS THERE!
TOUCHDOWN FOR MICHAEL IRVIN.
>> YO, JERRY JONES IS GONNA
CALL ME AFTER HE SEES THIS.
>> ANOTHER TOUCHDOWN
ON DAWAN OWENS,
NO STOPS AFTER TWO PLAYS.
HE'S DEFINITELY IN TROUBLE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THAT AGAIN.
MICHAEL IRVIN, TOUCHDOWN!
DIVING CATCH BY THE PLAYMAKER!
>> I FEEL LIKE TELLING YOU
A ROUTE AND SEE IF YOU CAN
STOP IT.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> NEXT UP, JOE NUMBER 3,
AARON McKEEVER.
AARON'S LOOKING PRETTY GOOD,
EXCEPT IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S
WEARING SOME BOXERS UNDER HIS
PANTS.
[LAUGHTER]
AARON NEEDS A STOP HERE
ON IRVIN TO TIE JAY
AND STAY IN THIS GAME.
HERE GOES MIKE.
ANOTHER GO ROUTE.
OH, AND HE BLOWS BY AARON.
ANOTHER TOUCHDOWN CATCH.
>> TOUCHDOWN!
>> TWO DOWN, TWO TDs AGAINST
JOE NUMBER 3, AARON McKEEVER.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT, BABY?
>> OH, I'M GOOD.
I'M PISSED 'CAUSE YOU GOT
THAT TOUCHDOWN.
>> NEXT UP, JAY McKEOWN.
HE'S IN THE LEAD WITH ONE STOP
AND HE CAN WIN THE MATCH-UP WITH
ANOTHER STOP RIGHT HERE, AND IT
LOOKS LIKE THE PROS ARE CALLING
A TIME-OUT.
>> THIS IS WHAT I CALL
"THE FEED YOU TECHNIQUE."
I'M GONNA CATCH IT, STOP SHORT,
BUT I'M GONNA HAND HIM BACK THAT
BALL AND SAY, "COME AND GET IT."
I'M GONNA FEED IT TO HIM.
>> LET'S TAKE IT TO HIM THEN.
>> MAKES IT EASIER.
>> HUGE PLAY RIGHT HERE.
IF JAY GETS A STOP, HE WILL WIN
MATCH-UP ONE.
>> HEY, MIKE, I NEED YOU
TO SCORE, OK?
>> OH, I WILL; DON'T WORRY.
>> COME ON, HURRICANE.
>> COME ON, PLAYMAKER.
LET'S GO, BABY.
>> JAY McKEOWN
VS. MICHAEL IRVIN.
IRVIN WITH A STOP ROUTE
AND A LITTLE BIT OF A STUMBLE,
AND THAT BALL IS INCOMPLETE.
JAY WINS THE MATCH-UP
WITH TWO STOPS.
>> WHOO!
GOOD LORD.
THAT'S WHAT THE GOOD LORD'S FOR
NOW.
>> McKEOWN, WITH TIGHT COVERAGE
ON THE PLAYMAKER.
THAT GIVES JAY TWO STOPS
AND A VICTORY.
CONGRATULATIONS TO JAY McKEOWN.
YOU'RE ONE STEP CLOSER TO GOING
TO OVERTIME.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR MATCH-UP TWO,
GUYS.
HIT THE LOCKER ROOM AND GO GET
READY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE RUNNING FOR YOUR
LIVES IN THE OCTAGON AGAINST
RANDY COUTURE.
>> I'M NOT A COWBOYS FAN,
BUT YOU GOT TO GIVE HIM
HIS PROPS FOR BEING A BAD DUDE.
>> IF IT WASN'T ON BEFORE,
IT'S ON NOW.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WELL, AT LEAST MICHAEL IRVIN
DIDN'T TOUCH MY ASS.
THAT'S ALL I GOT TO SAY.
HA HA HA!
>> RANDY, IT'S YOUR TURN.
>> IT'S MY TURN.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> SUBMIT THESE GUYS
AS MANY TIMES AS POSSIBLE.
>> WHAT HAPPENS IF ONE OF THEM
[BLEEPS] HIMSELF?
>> IF I GET A REAR NAKED CHOKE
ON A GUY AND HE DOESN'T TAP OUT,
HE'LL PASS OUT, AND THEN THAT
HAS HAPPENED.
>> HE LOSES HIS BOWEL MOVEMENTS,
AND WE GOT WAIVERS AGAINST THAT,
RIGHT?
>> WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT HAS HAPPENED?
YOU MEAN THE CAT--
>> THEY LOSE CONTROL.
>> YEAH, YOU LOSE CONTROL
OF YOUR BOWELS, DUDE.
>> YOU HAVE CHOKED SOMEBODY
AND "BOOM"?
>> YEAH.
>> WOW, MAN.
THAT'S JUST--THAT'S NASTY, MAN.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> IT AIN'T RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT NO PART OF THAT.
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> YOU GUYS LOOK LIKE A FUNERAL
CAVALCADE.
GET IN HERE.
JOES, WELCOME TO THE OCTAGON
FOR MATCH-UP TWO.
ARE YOU SCARED?
'CAUSE I'M SCARED, AND I'M NOT
EVEN FIGHTING.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA BE GRAPPLING
WITH RANDY COUTURE,
14-TIME UFC WINNER.
EACH OF YOU IS GONNA HAVE
5 MINUTES WITH RANDY COUTURE.
WHEN THE JOES CAN'T TAKE
ANY MORE PAIN, YOU GOT TO TAP
OUT, AND THEN THE FIGHT WILL
CONTINUE.
WHOEVER TAPS OUT THE LEAST IS
GOING TO WIN MATCH-UP TWO.
FIRST UP, JOE NUMBER 3,
AARON McKEEVER.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
>> ...DON'T STICK YOUR HEAD UP.
>> YOU MIGHT RECOGNIZE OUR
OFFICIAL, BIG JOHN McCARTHY,
13-YEAR VET OF THE UFC.
HE'S GONNA MAKE SURE THE JOES
GET BACK UP FOR MORE PUNISHMENT
AFTER THEY TAP OUT.
>> HERE WE GO.
ARE YOU READY?
YOU READY?
LET'S GET IT ON.
>> HERE WE GO.
AARON'S GAME IS BASEBALL.
RANDY COUTURE FEELS AT HOME
IN THE OCTAGON.
COUTURE IS STARING HIM DOWN,
HOLDING ONTO THAT HEAD.
AARON IS WINDMILLING LIKE
A 6-YEAR-OLD IN A FIGHT
WITH HIS BIG BROTHER!
LOOK AT THE FEAR OF GOD IN
HIS EYES, AND COUTURE WILL GET
HIM BACK, TAKES HIM TO THE
FENCE, AND SLAMS HIM DOWN.
>> OH!
>> THERE'S A LEG LOCK
AND OUR FIRST TAP.
AARON McKEEVER WITH ONE TAP
AND A PAIN LIKE HE'S NEVER FELT
IN HIS LIFE.
>> GOOD JOB, BABY.
>> SOMEBODY BRING
THE OXYGEN TANKS.
>> RANDY'S GOT AARON UP AGAINST
THE FENCE, AND HE'S GOING
FOR THE KNEE.
OH, HE'S DOWN.
McKEEVER'S DOWN.
FIGHTING HARD, THOUGH,
AND GROANING A LOT.
>> [LOUD GRUNTING]
>> THOSE ARE NOT SOUNDS OF JOY.
AND THAT'S A TAP.
THAT'S TWO TAPS
FOR AARON McKEEVER.
TWO TAPS.
RANDY COUTURE EARNED THAT ONE,
THOUGH.
>> DUDE, HE [BLEEP] HIM UP,
I'M TELLING YOU.
I'M TELLING YOU, HE HURT HIM.
>> COUTURE'S COMING AGAIN.
HE'S GOING DOWN INTO THE FENCE
AND DOWN AGAIN.
COUTURE'S WORKING
ON THAT SHOULDER.
WORKING ON THE RIGHT SHOULDER
OF AARON McKEEVER.
>> THE SHOULDER'S WEAK.
>> I CAN TELL PAIN.
THAT LAST THING HE DID HURT,
DIDN'T IT?
>> OH! OK!
>> STOP IT RIGHT THERE.
>> THAT'S 3 TAPS.
>> HE COULDN'T TAP.
HE HAD HIS HANDS LIKE THIS.
>> McKEEVER IS NOT ENJOYING THIS
RIGHT NOW.
COME ON, AARON.
YOU'RE DOING ALL RIGHT, BABY.
RANDY COUTURE IN CONTROL
OF AARON McKEEVER'S BODY.
HE'S GOT HIM DOWN AGAIN.
>> OH, OH, IT'S A WRAP.
IT'S A WRAP.
>> [GRUNTING]
OK!
>> STOP RIGHT THERE.
>> THAT'S 4 TAPS.
McKEEVER GETTING UP SLOW, TRYING
TO KILL THE CLOCK.
HERE COMES COUTURE.
COUTURE'S AFTER HIM AGAIN.
MAN, THIS WOULD SUCK TO HAVE
TO DO.
McKEEVER, NOT SHOWING ANY FEAR,
SLAMMED DOWN AGAIN.
COUTURE ON TOP OF HIM.
>> OH! OH!
>> THAT'S THE OLD FIGURE-4
LEG LOCK.
THERE'S ANOTHER TAP.
THAT'S 5 TAPS
FOR AARON McKEEVER, 5 TAPS.
>> THAT IS ABSOLUTELY SICK.
>> HERE WE GO AGAIN.
RANDY COUTURE COMING AGAIN
AFTER AARON McKEEVER.
MAN, THIS IS NO JOKE.
>> [GROANING]
>> OH, THE REAR NAKED CHOKE.
>> THERE'S ANOTHER TAP.
>> DID YOU SEE THAT?
>> 6 TAPS, 6 TAPS
FOR AARON McKEEVER.
HE JUST WANTS THIS TO BE OVER.
>> YEAH, SHAKE THAT OFF, BOY.
>> DAMN.
>> COUTURE, TAKING HIM DOWN
ONCE AGAIN.
AARON McKEEVER'S NOT GIVING UP,
SHOWING A LOT OF GUTS HERE
IN THE OCTAGON.
>> COME ON, KEEP UP WITH IT.
OH, MY!
>> AND THAT'S AN ARM BAR,
I BELIEVE.
>> THAT HURT UP HERE.
>> AND THAT IS 7 TAPS
FOR AARON McKEEVER, AND HE IS
GONNA FEEL ALL OF THEM
IN THE MORNING.
>> IT TAKES SOME COURAGE TO GET
IN THAT OCTAGON, BUDDY.
I'M NOT COMING IN THERE WITHOUT
A BAT.
I WON'T DO IT.
>> GOOD JOB, AARON.
GOOD JOB, BABY.
>> ONE DOWN, ONE DOWN.
TWO TO GO.
>> OK.
>> HE WAS REAL, REAL TENSE
FOR THE FIRST MINUTE.
>> OH.
>> SPENT ALL HIS ENERGY IN THAT.
>> [GASPING]
"DON'T HURT ME."
>> IT TAKES SO MUCH ENERGY,
THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> NO DOUBT, BABY.
>> HERE WE GO.
JAY IS A CLOSE-COMBAT INSTRUCTOR
FOR THE U.S. ARMY RESERVES,
SO HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
FIVE MINUTES.
>> OK, HERE WE GO.
ARE YOU READY?
YOU READY?
LET'S GET IT ON.
>> DON'T YOU TAP OUT TOO FAST.
>> RANDY'S GOING AFTER HIM
RIGHT AWAY--OH, WOW!
RANDY JUST BODY-SLAMMED HIM!
>> THERE'S THE ARM BAR.
>> THERE'S THE TAP.
ONE TAP FOR JAY McKEOWN.
>> YEAH, NOTHING YOU COULD DO
ABOUT THAT ONE.
>> THE CLOCK IS RUNNING.
>> COME ON, RANDY.
>> ONCE AGAIN, A SLAM
TO THE GROUND RANDY JUST THREW
ON TOP OF JAY McKEOWN.
OOH, ANOTHER ARM BAR
AND ANOTHER TAP.
>> GONNA BREAK A RECORD
ON THESE TAPS.
>> HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YO, LET'S GET IT UP.
>> WOW.
>> COMING UP ON "PROS
VS. JOES"...
RANDY COULD SNAP THAT ARM
IN HALF AT ANY MOMENT.
CANSECO'S ON FIRE.
THE JOES ARE IN BIG TROUBLE
TONIGHT.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "PROS
VS. JOES."
WE'RE IN MATCH-UP TWO,
WHERE RANDY COUTURE ALREADY GOT
AARON McKEEVER TO TAP OUT
7 TIMES.
>> OH!
>> NOW HE'S RUINING
JAY McKEOWN'S LIFE, TOO.
HE'S TAPPED OUT TWICE, AND WE'RE
ONLY ONE MINUTE IN.
RANDY'S GOT HIM DOWN.
JAY IS A CLOSE-COMBAT INSTRUCTOR
FOR THE U.S. ARMY RESERVE.
AND IF HE GETS OUT OF THIS,
THEN HE'S REALLY DOING
SOMETHING.
>> HE'S TRYING TO STAY LOCKED
ON HIM.
>> HE'S TRYING TO NOT GET CHOKED
OUT, PUT THAT LEG IN, HOLD
HIS HANDS.
HE'S GOT A LITTLE EXPERIENCE.
>> RANDY'S TWISTING THAT FOOT,
AND JAY JUMPS LOOSE.
WHAT A MOVE!
OH, RANDY'S REELING HIM BACK IN.
>> YEAH.
IT'S A DIFFERENT BALL GAME NOW,
BABY.
>> AND RANDY RETALIATES WITH
A CHOKE.
>> THERE'S THE TAP.
THAT'S 3 TAPS FOR JAY McKEOWN.
>> SURE TIRING, AIN'T IT?
IT'S TIRING.
HA HA HA!
>> JAY McKEOWN DOING A GREAT JOB
HERE VS. RANDY COUTURE.
THE CLOCK IS RUNNING.
>> HE AIN'T NO JOKE.
>> RANDY, TAKING HIM DOWN.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> COME ON, RANDY.
YOU KNOW HIM NOW.
YEAH, YOU KNOW HIM NOW.
>> HE'S REALLY DOING SOMETHING.
>> AND RANDY MANAGES TO GET
THE ARM BAR, AND THERE'S
THE TAP.
THAT IS 4 TAPS FOR JAY McKEOWN.
JAY'S GOT A LOT OF TATTOOS
ON HIM; I HOPE HE'S GOT
HIS MEDICAL INFORMATION TATTOOED
ON HIM, TOO.
RANDY TAKES HIM DOWN AGAIN.
OH, BUT LOOK AT THAT!
JAY GETS HIM IN THE HEAD LOCK.
A JOE WITH THE OFFENSIVE MOVE.
IMPRESSIVE!
OH, BUT RANDY REVERSES IT,
GOES BACK TO PUNISHING JAY!
THERE GOES HIS MOUTHPIECE.
OH, HE'S FALLING APART IN THERE!
>> STOP RIGHT THERE.
>> THERE'S ANOTHER TAP.
THAT IS 5 TAPS.
>> PUT YOUR MOUTHPIECE IN.
>> MAN, THAT'S A LONG-ASS TIME,
AIN'T IT?
>> YEP.
>> FIVE TAPS FOR JAY McKEOWN.
REMEMBER, AARON HAD 7, SO JAY
CAN ONLY TAP OUT ONE MORE TIME
TO MOVE INTO FIRST PLACE.
>> YOU HAVEN'T THROWN UP YET.
YOU'RE DOING FINE.
LET'S GO.
>> 30 SECONDS.
>> TAP HIS ASS OUT
ONE MORE TIME.
COME ON.
>> ANYTHING UNDER DOUBLE FIGURES
HERE IS PRETTY RESPECTABLE
FOR ALL THE JOES.
HE'S GOT HIM IN A HEAD LOCK
THERE, TURNING IT AROUND ON HIM.
>> START COUNTING SOME SHEEP.
>> TAP HIM OFF.
YOU'RE GONNA TAP OUT.
LET'S GO, BABY.
LET'S GO, RANDY.
>> OH, HE BREAKS THE HOLD!
WHAT A MOVE!
TEN SECONDS LEFT.
HANG IN THERE, JAY.
COUTURE WANTS ONE MORE TAP.
>> COME ON, JAY.
>> JAY REFUSES TO TAP OUT.
HE'S DOING A GREAT JOB, MAN.
[BELL RINGS]
AND THAT'S THE BELL.
JAY McKEOWN FINISHES
WITH 5 TAPS AND TAKES THE LEAD.
IT'S CLEAR THAT HIS ARMY
TRAINING HELPED.
>> WHOO!
THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> McKEOWN FOUGHT HIS ASS OFF
AND EVEN WENT ON THE OFFENSIVE
AGAINST RANDY COUTURE.
THIS IS ONE JOE WHO WAS NOT
AFRAID.
>> YOU WERE DOING A GOOD JOB
OF JUST HOLDING ONTO AN ARM
FOR CONTROL.
>> YEAH.
I'M ACTUALLY A CLOSE-COMBAT
INSTRUCTOR IN THE ARMY.
BUT I KNOW ANYTHING I TRIED
TO DO WOULD MAKE IT WORSE.
>> YEAH.
PLUS, AS YOU'RE GETTING OLDER,
IT'S TOUGH TO GET HIM OFF YOU.
I WORK OUT WITH HIM ALL
THE TIME.
>> HE GOT ALONG.
HE GOT SOME FREQUENT FLYER
MILES, THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> HE GOT UP AND DOWN.
>> I LIKE THAT:
"THEY HAVE A LITTLE FREQUENT
FLYER MILES."
RANDY, YOU GOT [INDISTINCT].
I LIKE THAT [INDISTINCT].
HA HA HA!
>> NEXT UP, JOE NUMBER ONE,
DAWAN OWENS.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO.
YOU READY?
LET'S GET IT ON!
COME ON.
>> HERE WE GO.
RANDY COUTURE, STARING DOWN
DAWAN OWENS LIKE A FAT KID
STARING AT A DOUGHNUT.
>> GET HIM, RANDY!
>> DAWAN'S MOVING AROUND.
DAWAN'S GOT ENERGY, BUT THAT
ENERGY GOES QUICK.
DAWAN OWENS IS A STAND-UP COMIC
AND A JOCULAR GUY, BUT NOT
LAUGHING NOW.
>> I CAN SMELL TAP.
>> STOP RIGHT THERE.
>> OH, MY!
>> AND THAT'S A TAP.
ONE TAP FOR DAWAN OWENS.
>> THAT WAS A NEW MOVE.
>> HE MUST HAVE SAVED THE BEST
FOR YOU RIGHT THERE.
YOU'RE THE BIG BOY.
>> JAY McKEOWN REALLY CHEERING
FOR RANDY COUTURE NOW.
HE'S SMELLING OVERTIME.
DAWAN OWENS LOSES HERE,
JAY McKEOWN'S GOING STRAIGHT
INTO OVERTIME.
>> FOLD UP LIKE A CHURCH CHAIR.
>> OH, AND THERE'S ANOTHER
ARM BAR, PULLING HIS ARM OUT OF
HIS SOCKET, AND THERE'S THE TAP.
THAT'S TWO TAPS FOR DAWAN OWENS.
>> I'M GOING FOR 8 TAPS.
>> HALL-OF-FAMER RANDY COUTURE
TURNING THIS INTO A HALL OF PAIN
FOR ALL OUR JOES.
>> STOP RIGHT THERE.
>> AND THERE'S ANOTHER TAP.
THREE TAPS FOR DAWAN OWENS.
>> OH, JEEZ!
AND WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
>> DAWAN CAN ONLY TAP OUT
ONE MORE TIME TO BEAT JAY
AND WIN MATCH-UP TWO.
RANDY COUTURE, TRYING TO GET
DAWAN ON DOWN; DAWAN DOING
A GOOD JOB KEEPING HIS FEET,
COUTURE WRESTLING HIM DOWN.
>> DON'T DO IT.
>> DAWAN, OBVIOUSLY
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE RIGHT NOW.
>> STOP RIGHT THERE.
>> AND THAT'S A TAP.
THAT REAR NAKED CHOKE GIVES US
TAP NUMBER 4.
>> NO REST, BABY, NO REST.
>> I'M NOT SURE HOW RELIGIOUS
DAWAN IS, BUT WE'RE ALL PRAYING
FOR THIS TO BE OVER PRETTY QUICK
FOR HIM.
RANDY COUTURE DOES NOT STOP.
RANDY COUTURE, TAKING HIM DOWN
WITH THE RIGHT HAND.
GOT HIM IN A GUILLOTINE.
THERE'S ANOTHER TAP.
>> [COUGHING]
>> THAT IS 5 TAPS
FOR DAWAN OWENS.
>> DID YOU LEAVE A WILL?
>> ONE MORE TAP AND JAY McKEOWN
WINS AND EARNS A BYE
INTO OVERTIME.
APPROACHING 20 SECONDS LEFT.
JAY CAN SMELL OVERTIME NOW.
RANDY COUTURE, HOOKING
THAT SHOULDER.
>> DON'T LET HIM GET THAT.
>> ONLY 13 SECONDS.
IF HE CAN JUST ENDURE THE--
OH, THE PAIN!
TEN SECONDS.
LOOK AT DAWAN'S FACE.
>> SUPER ATHLETE.
>> THE HORROR!
>> FOUR SECONDS.
CAN HE DO IT?
>> STOP RIGHT THERE.
>> THAT'S 6 TAP-OUTS,
AND THAT IS TIME, FOLKS.
JAY McKEOWN WINS MATCH-UP TWO,
TAPPING OUT 5 TIMES.
DAWAN FALLS SHORT BY ONE TAP
WITH 6.
THAT MEANS JAY EARNS A BYE GOING
INTO OVERTIME.
YOU DO NOT HAVE TO COMPETE
IN MATCH-UP 3.
DAWAN OWENS, AARON McKEEVER,
YOU GUYS ARE HEAD-TO-HEAD
IN MATCH-UP 3 VS. JOSE CANSECO
ON THE BASEBALL DIAMOND.
WHOEVER WINS IS GOING
INTO OVERTIME.
WHOEVER LOSES IS GOING HOME.
>> OH, I'M SPENT!
>> WHOO!
>> IS YOUR NECK LIKE--MY NECK
IS LIKE--
>> OH, MAN.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT THE WORST
THING FOR ME WAS: WHEN HE DID
THE GUILLOTINE, JUST--
>> NO, I DON'T WANT TO FEEL IT.
>> WHEN HE GOT YOUR HAND
LIKE THIS AND LEANED BACK?
>> YEAH.
>> MAN, TALKING ABOUT SOME
INTENSE PAIN ON THE NECK.
MY NECK RIGHT NOW FEELS LIKE IT
JUST GOT STRETCHED OUT AND PUT
BACK, AND IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S PAIN?
THE ARM BAR ON MY ELBOW, AND I
FELT IT STARTING TO CRACK, AND
I'M, LIKE, TAP.
>> YEAH, THIS DUDE POPPED TWICE.
>> POP, POP?
>> THAT WAS HIS SHOULDER.
>> THAT WAS YOUR SHOULDER
POPPING?
>> MY SHOULDER, YEAH.
>> THE REALITY IS, I'M NOT EVEN
REALLY KNOWN AS A SUBMISSION
GUY.
I MEAN, I'M A GOOD WRESTLER--
>> WELL, I'M BETTING YOU ARE
NOW, FOR SURE.
>> ON THE GROUND, I WAS MORE
A BROWN-AND-POUND GUY.
I WOULD JUST HIT YOU IN THE HEAD
TILL THE REFEREE STOPPED
THE FIGHT.
I ONLY HAD, IN ALL MY FIGHTS,
YOU KNOW, TWO SUBMISSIONS
IN 22 FIGHTS.
>> YOU MADE JOSE'S JOB VERY--
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS ALREADY EASY, BUT YOU
MADE IT MORE EASY.
>> THEY GOT TO GO SWING A BAT
NOW?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
>> WHAT YOU'RE GONNA HEAR IS
A DIFFERENT SOUND COMING OFF
OF MY BAT THAN THEIR BAT.
>> OH, YES!
>> JOES, READY FOR YOUR FINAL
MATCH-UP?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SO IT ALL COMES DOWN
TO THIS FOR DAWAN OWENS
AND AARON McKEEVER.
WHOEVER WINS HERE GOES
TO OVERTIME WITH JAY McKEOWN.
THE OTHER IS HEADED HOME.
STRAIGHT UP, FOR MATCH-UP 3,
YOU'RE GONNA BE TAKING ON JOSE
CANSECO IN A HOME-RUN DERBY.
YOU GET 5 OUTS.
ANYTHING OTHER THAN A HOME RUN
IS AN OUT.
NOW, IT'S GONNA BE DIFFERENT
FROM A NORMAL HOME-RUN DERBY
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA GIVE YOU
EXTRA RUNS FOR DISTANCE.
IF YOU GET IT OVER THE FIRST
FENCE, THAT'S ONE RUN;
SECOND FENCE, TWO RUNS;
THIRD FENCE, 3 RUNS;
FOURTH FENCE, 4 RUNS.
WHOEVER CAN COME CLOSEST TO
JOSE CANSECO'S SCORE OUT HERE
IS GOING TO GO TO OVERTIME.
LET'S GET THIS THING CRACKING.
CRUSH IT!
>> WELL, THAT'S ONE.
>> AND THAT IS A WELL-HIT BALL.
THAT ONE'S GOING WAY OVER
THE FOURTH WALL.
>> YES, SIR, YES, SIR.
>> THAT IS WORTH 4 RUNS,
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
NO PUN INTENDED.
>> YEAH, THAT'S GONE, TOO.
THAT'S GONE.
>> THAT'S ANOTHER 4 RUNS
FOR JOSE CANSECO.
THAT IS A TOTAL OF 8.
JOSE CANSECO LOOKING
PRETTY GOOD.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> UPPER DECK.
>> THAT WOULD BE 19 RUNS,
NO OUTS!
>> OH, JEEZ.
>> OH, YEAH.
THOSE ARE JUST FLY BALLS.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT, JOSE.
>> CANSECO'S ON FIRE!
THE JOES ARE IN BIG TROUBLE
TONIGHT.
COMING UP ON "PROS VS. JOES"...
FINAL OUT FOR AARON McKEEVER.
HE NEEDS AT LEAST 3 RUNS TO BEAT
DAWAN AND GO TO OVERTIME.
>> I'M HITTING THIS OUT.
OOF!
AND NO OUT
VS. JOES" HOME-RUN DERBY.
FOUL BALL.
CANSECO WITH HIS FIRST OUT.
YOU GET 5 OUTS IN THIS GAME,
SO HE'S GOT 4 OUTS LEFT.
TWO OUTS FOR JOSE CANSECO.
>> LOCK IT BACK DOWN, BABY.
>> THAT'S GONNA BE OUT NUMBER 3.
19 RUNS, 3 OUTS.
CANSECO STILL HAS TWO MORE OUTS
LEFT.
WHAT A SHOT!
23 RUNS.
CALL NASA!
THAT ONE'S LAUNCHED!
GET ME SOME NURSES OUT HERE,
MAN!
HE'S PUTTING ON A CLINIC!
[LAUGHTER]
>> WHOO!
>> LOVE IT, Y'ALL.
>> CRUSHED!
THAT'S 38 RUNS AND 3 OUTS.
>> 42!
>> OH, NO!
>> JOSE'S STRING OF LONG BALLS
COMES TO AN END.
HE HAS ONE OUT LEFT WITH 50 RUNS
ON THE BOARD.
FOUR OUTS.
FINAL OUT FOR JOSE CANSECO.
>> I TOLD YOU.
>> HA HA HA!
>> STROKING.
54!
>> PUT THE LIGHT OUT, BABY!
>> JOSE CANSECO PUTTING ON
A SHOW FOR THE PEOPLE
AT THE HOME DEPOT CENTER.
>> YEAH.
>> COME ON, JOSE, MAN.
THIS IS GETTING A BIT
RIDICULOUS!
>> 58 RUNS FOR JOSE CANSECO,
HANGING ON ON THE LAST OUT.
>> STOP IT, MAN, JUST STOP IT!
>> 70 RUNS!
>> OH, JEEZ.
>> THAT'S A GOOD YEAR
RIGHT THERE, BABY.
THAT'S A GOOD YEAR RIGHT THERE.
>> AND THAT IS JOSE'S FIFTH
AND FINAL OUT.
HE FINISHES WITH AN AMAZING
70 RUNS.
>> THAT'S A PRO RIGHT THERE,
BABY.
>> HOW ABOUT THEM LATINO
BROTHERS NOW?
THEY'RE FINE NOW, AIN'T THEY?
>> DAWAN OWENS IS UP FIRST
FOR THE JOES.
HE HAS 5 OUTS HERE TO TRY
TO CATCH JOSE.
>> UH, YOU USE SOME JUICE?
YOU USE SOME STEROIDS
OR SOMETHING, BROTHER?
BECAUSE YOU'LL NEVER BEAT 70,
AND BY THE WAY, GIVE MY DAUGHTER
BACK HER BAT WHEN YOU'RE
FINISHED WITH IT, OK?
>> HA HA!
>> FIRST PITCH.
>> OH, NO.
>> IT'S A FOUL BALL, AND THAT IS
ONE OUT.
>> NERVOUS.
LACTIC ACID BUILDING UP
IN THE MUSCLES.
>> DAWAN OWENS.
>> TWO OUTS.
HEY, CALL HIS CAR.
SOMEBODY CALL HIS CAR AND CALL
THE AIRPORT.
>> NO RUNS.
>> WE'RE ABOUT TO TELL THE
AIRLINES YOU ARE ON YOUR WAY.
>> OH!
>> WAIT A MINUTE!
>> HE WOKE UP OUT OF THE GRAVE!
>> HE GETS ALL OF THAT ONE!
IT'S OVER THE FOURTH WALL!
FOUR RUNS, TWO OUTS
FOR DAWAN OWENS.
SHOWING SOME SIGNS OF LIFE!
>> DON'T LET A 42-YEAR-OLD MAN
THAT LOST HIS STEP HUMILIATE
YOU.
MM-MMM.
DON'T DO IT.
>> OH, I PISSED YOU OFF,
DIDN'T I?
PISSED YOU OFF, DIDN'T I?
>> THAT IS WORTH 4 RUNS.
>> THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
>> EIGHT RUNS, TWO OUTS
FOR DAWAN OWENS.
IS THAT GOOD ENOUGH?
THAT'S GONNA BE WORTH 4.
THAT'S 20 RUNS FOR DAWAN OWENS
AFTER 5 STRAIGHT JACKS, AND HE
STILL ONLY HAS TWO OUTS.
>> YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT BAD.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> AH!
THREE OUTS.
OH, MY.
>> THREE DOWN.
>> ONLY TWO OUTS LEFT FOR DAWAN.
>> BUT YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY:
"IT AIN'T OVER TILL IT'S OVER"
IN BASEBALL.
>> IT'S OVER FOR THIS GUY.
>> AND THAT IS ANOTHER OUT.
TWENTY RUNS AND 4 OUTS
FOR DAWAN OWENS.
TELL JOE IF HE MIGHT RELAX
A LITTLE BIT, HIT A BALL.
>> TELL A FEW JOKES, SEE IF YOU
CAN MAKE THE BALL LAUGH OVER
THE FENCE.
>> DOWN TO HIS FINAL OUT IS
DAWAN OWENS.
CAN HE FIND A WAY TO RALLY ON
HIS LAST OUT?
>> YEAH, YOU NEED A LOT
OF THOSE 4s RIGHT NOW.
>> AND THAT'S GONNA DO IT
FOR DAWAN OWENS, HIS FIFTH
AND FINAL OUT.
>> GOOD NIGHT, SWEETHEART!
>> HE FINISHES WITH 20 RUNS.
THAT'S 50 LESS THAN JOSE.
AARON McKEEVER IS UP NEXT.
HE NEEDS AT LEAST 21 RUNS
TO WIN THE MATCH-UP AND JOIN
JAY McKEOWN IN OVERTIME.
McKEEVER HAS A BACKGROUND
IN BASEBALL, PITCHED A NO-HITTER
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
>> OH.
>> POP-UP.
THAT IS THE FIRST OUT
FOR AARON McKEEVER.
>> GOT JAMMED WITH
A 20-MILE-PER-HOUR FASTBALL.
>> POPS UP ANOTHER.
TWO OUTS IN A ROW.
>> YEAH, HERE WE GO.
>> THREE OUTS.
ONLY TWO OUTS LEFT FOR AARON.
>> TWO OUTS LEFT.
YOU WON'T GET TO THE 7s.
>> OH!
RIPS AT THAT ONE, GETS A PIECE.
THAT'S OVER THE THIRD WALL.
THAT'S 3 RUNS.
>> THAT'S A LONG WAY TO 70.
>> AND HE RIPS THAT ONE.
LINE-DRIVE FOR McKEEVER.
IS IT GONNA GET OVER.?
ONE RUN.
AARON McKEEVER'S GOT 4 RUNS.
THAT'S 16 AWAY FROM DAWAN,
66 AWAY FROM JOSE.
>> HA HA HA!
>> GETS HOLD OF THAT ONE.
>> OH, NO!
>> AARON McKEEVER, LOOKING
PRETTY STRONG.
FOUR MORE RUNS
FOR AARON McKEEVER.
HE IS AT 8.
McKEEVER GETS A HOLD OF THAT
ONE.
>> COME ON, BABY.
>> THAT IS 3.
ELEVEN RUNS.
>> HE THINKS HE CAN COMPETE NOW.
>> AARON McKEEVER, LOOKING
VERY CONFIDENT.
STEPPING IN ONCE MORE.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> McKEEVER POPS ANOTHER ONE UP.
>> POP'S GONE.
>> THREE RUNS.
McKEEVER, LOOKING CANSECO-ESQUE
IN THE BOX, HAVING SOME JOE
SUCCESS TONIGHT.
>> COME ON, NOW.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA IMPRESS ME
UNLESS YOU HIT IT AT LEAST
400 FEET.
>> OH!
>> OH, McKEEVER WITH A GRUNT,
BUT IT'S A FOUL BALL.
>> FOUL BALL.
>> FOUR OUTS FOR McKEEVER.
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO THIS.
FINAL OUT FOR AARON McKEEVER.
HE NEEDS AT LEAST 3 RUNS TO BEAT
DAWAN AND GO TO OVERTIME.
>> I'M HITTING THIS OUT.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> AARON McKEEVER GETS A HOLD
OF THAT ONE.
>> GET THE [BLEEP] OUTTA HERE!
>> IT MIGHT MAKE IT TO THE--MAN!
>> YEAH!
>> AARON McKEEVER GETS
TO THE SEATS.
THE WALK-OFF HOME RUN GIVES
AARON 4 RUNS.
HE FINISHES WITH A TOTAL
OF 22 RUNS...
>> COME ON!
>> AND THAT GIVES HIM
THE VICTORY.
>> COME ON, MICHAEL.
WHOO!
>> AARON McKEEVER, PUTTING ON
A GOOD SHOW.
THAT LONG BALL EARNS HIM
THE PLAY OF THE DAY, SPONSORED
BY DR. PEPPER.
THERE'S MORE TO IT!
THAT MEANS AARON McKEEVER
AND JAY McKEOWN, JOES NUMBER 2
AND 3, ADVANCING TO OVERTIME.
DAWAN OWENS CAME CLOSE,
BUT IT WASN'T ENOUGH!
HE'S HEADED HOME TO LICK
HIS WOUNDS.
OK, LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
THE TOYOTA SCOREBOARD.
TOYOTA, MOVING FORWARD.
GONNA BE JAY McKEOWN TAKING ON
AARON McKEEVER IN OVERTIME.
>> I THINK YOU BROKE A LIGHT.
>> THAT WAS A LITTLE BIT
TOO EASY.
I DIDN'T EXPECT IT TO BE
THAT MUCH OF A SLAUGHTER.
>> 70.
COME ON, MAN.
>> IT'S JUST...
TOO EASY.
>> SHOW TIME.
>> WHOO!
>> YOU AND ME.
>> I'M WITH YOU, BABY.
IT'S ON.
>> YOU'RE MINE, BITCH.
>> COMING UP IN OVERTIME,
HE'S DOMINATING INSIDE.
>> [BLEEP]
>> JAY TAKES THE JERSEY OFF.
HERE COMES AARON McKEEVER!
HERE COMES AARON McKEEVER!JARED HEE
HERE COMES AARON McKEEVER!JARED HE.
AND A DELICIOU
AND A DELICIOUS FOOT-LON
HERE COMES AARON McKEEVER!JARED HE.
AND A DELICIOUS FOOT-LONG
SUBW
HERE COMES AARON McKEEVER!JARED HE.
AND A DELICIOUS FOOT-LONG
SUBWAY CLUB,
MICHAEL STRAHAN HERE.
LESS THAN HALF THE FAT
OF A McDonald's BIG MAC--
BUT TWICE THE MEAT,
SO IT FILLS ME UP WITHOUT
SLOWIN' ME DOWN.
- LESS FAT... LESS FAT.
- MORE MEAT... MORE MEAT.
LESS FAT, LESS FAT.
MORE MEAT.
( both laughing )
MORE MEAT!
>> GENTLEMEN, WELCOME TO THE
MAJESTY THAT IS OVERTIME
ON "PROS VS. JOES," HERE AT
THE HOME DEPOT CENTER.
>> LET'S HAVE SOME FUN.
>> JAY AND AARON, BOTH OF YOU
BATTLED HARD, YOU'VE SHOWN GREAT
COURAGE.
YOU DESERVE TO BE HERE.
JAY, GREAT IN THE OCTAGON, GREAT
IN FOOTBALL VS. MICHAEL IRVIN.
AARON, YOU HAD A GREAT COMEBACK
ON THE HOME-RUN DERBY
VS. JOSE CANSECO.
>> YOU GUYS BARELY SURVIVED
THE FIRST ROUND; HOPEFULLY
YOU CAN SURVIVE THIS ONE.
>> YOU GUYS AREN'T QUITE THERE
YET.
YOUR AGILITY, YOUR STRENGTH,
YOUR SPEED, AND MOST OF ALL,
YOUR DETERMINATION IS ABOUT
TO BE TESTED.
>> THE FUN IS DONE.
OVERTIME IS "WIN OR GO HOME."
>> OK, HERE'S HOW THE OVERTIME
WORKS.
EACH OF YOU WILL GO HEAD-TO-HEAD
AGAINST ALL 4 PROS IN 4
CONSECUTIVE TIME-BASED EVENTS.
FIRST UP, YOU'LL HIT THE
HARDWOOD, BATTLING KEVIN WILLIS
FOR REBOUND SUPREMACY.
NEXT, YOU'LL SHOW OFF YOUR ARM
ON THE GRIDIRON, PLAYING
QUARTERBACK AGAINST MICHAEL
IRVIN.
THEN YOU'LL HEAD TO THE BASEBALL
DIAMOND, WHERE YOU'LL TRY TO GET
A HIT OFF JOSE CANSECO.
AND FINALLY, YOU'LL BATTLE
UFC LEGEND RANDY COUTURE AGAIN,
THIS TIME IN A WRESTLING MATCH.
THE JOE WHO FINISHES WITH THE
LOWEST CUMULATIVE TIME WILL WIN
THE SHIRTS OFF THESE PROS' BACKS
AND WILL QUALIFY FOR THE "PROS
VS. JOES" CHAMPIONSHIP,
WHERE THEY CAN WIN OUR GRAND
PRIZE AND A TOYOTA TUNDRA.
FOR THE FIRST EVENT IN OVERTIME,
THE JOES MUST GRAB TWO REBOUNDS
ON KEVIN WILLIS IN ONE MINUTE.
AARON'S UP FIRST.
>> I TOLD YOU, IT'S HELL IN
THE HOLE DOWN HERE, BIG FELLA.
HELL IN THE HOLE.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
>> HERE WE GO, TO GET IT
STARTED.
KEVIN WILLIS HAS DONE THIS
FOR 20 YEARS IN THE NBA.
OVER 11,000 REBOUNDS IN HIS
CAREER; THERE'S ANOTHER.
NEXT SHOT TOO EASY
FOR THE ALL-STAR.
HE'S DOMINATING INSIDE.
TIME'S TICKING, 30 SECONDS.
AARON STILL NEEDS TWO BOARDS.
AND WILLIS THROWS HIM
TO THE GROUND.
TOSSED LIKE RAGGEDY ANDY.
ANOTHER STRONG REBOUND
FOR KEVIN WILLIS.
AARON McKEEVER REALLY NEEDS
TO GET HIS GAME TOGETHER.
ANOTHER SHOT IN THE AIR.
OH, AARON McKEEVER RUNS IT DOWN!
ONE REBOUND!
AARON NEEDS ONE MORE TO FINISH
THIS EVENT.
OH, WILLIS GETS THE AIR BALL.
HERE COMES ANOTHER!
AARON'S GOT TO HURRY, AND HE
OUT-HUSTLES KEVIN TO THE BALL!
AND AARON GRABS HIS SECOND
REBOUND.
HE FINISHES IN 51 SECONDS.
NEXT UP, JAY McKEOWN.
>> I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
WE DO IT.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
>> OUR OVERTIME CLOCK
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY SUBWAY.
THIS IS GONNA BE TOUGH FOR 6'2"
JAY McKEOWN.
SECOND SHOT.
WILLIS CHASES IT DOWN.
JAYS GOT TO GET TO BALLS
LIKE THAT.
SO FAR, NO REBOUNDS--OH!
THERE'S A REBOUND
FOR JAY McKEOWN.
McKEOWN'S GOT ONE.
HE'S GOT TO FIGHT.
IF HE CAN GET ANOTHER, HE CAN
GET A LEG UP ON McKEEVER.
THAT ONE'S HEADED TO THE CORNER
AND WILLIS BEATS JAY
TO THE BALL.
NEXT SHOT'S UP, AND DOWN GOES
McKEOWN!
WILLIS IS JUST TOO PHYSICAL
INSIDE FOR THESE JOES!
McKEOWN'S GOT ONE SO FAR, AND
JAY McKEOWN WITH TWO REBOUNDS!
HE FINISHES IN 39 SECONDS,
SO AFTER ONE EVENT IN O.T.,
JAY TAKES A 12-SECOND LEAD.
THE SECOND EVENT IN OVERTIME IS
A GAME OF ACCURACY.
THE JOES MUST THROW ONE FOOTBALL
PAST MICHAEL IRVIN, BUT KEEP IT
INSIDE THE SURROUNDING BARRIER.
THEY GOT ONE MINUTE
TO GET IT DONE.
AARON'S UP FIRST.
HE DROPS BACK TO PASS.
THERE'S McKEEVER'S FIRST THROW,
AND THAT IS A LITTLE HIGH.
SECOND THROW FOR McKEEVER.
HE'LL TRY AGAIN.
OOH!
THAT ONE, MICHAEL IRVIN SNAGS
OUT OF THE SKY.
HERE COMES THE THIRD PASS.
WAY TOO HIGH.
McKEEVER'S GOT TO BRING IT DOWN.
McKEEVER WITH ANOTHER SHOT.
AGAIN, THAT BALL IS HIGH.
HE'S GOT THE ARM STRENGTH,
BUT AARON CAN'T SEEM TO FIND
THE ACCURACY.
MICHAEL IRVIN WITH HIS HANDS
ON THAT ONE.
OH, THAT ONE ALMOST SLIPPED
THROUGH THE PLAYMAKER'S FINGERS,
BUT HE HELD ON!
McKEEVER FIRES, TOO HIGH AGAIN.
>> LOOK LIKE HE'S WEARING DOWN,
MAN.
>> GUY'S GETTING A LITTLE TIRED
WITH THAT 3-STEP DROP.
McKEEVER--OH!
NOPE, NOT QUITE.
[AIR HORN BLOWS]
AND THAT IS A MAX-OUT TIME.
ONE MINUTE FOR AARON McKEEVER.
CUMULATIVE TIME RIGHT NOW
FOR AARON McKEEVER--ONE MINUTE,
51 SECONDS WITH THE MAX-OUT.
>> GOOD THROWS, THOUGH, BABY,
GOOD THROWS.
I MEAN, IF I WAS KEVIN WILLIS.
>> JAY'S GOT A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
HERE TO BUILD HIS LEAD OVER
AARON McKEEVER.
HE'S GOT TO THROW A FOOTBALL
PAST MICHAEL IRVIN BUT INSIDE
THE BARRIERS IN ONE MINUTE.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
SO FAR, JAY HAS WON EVERY EVENT
THAT HE'S BEEN IN.
THREE-STEP DROP.
THAT BALL RIGHT IN THE HANDS
OF THE PLAYMAKER.
HERE COMES THE SECOND PASS.
HE FIRES.
IRVIN WITH A NICE CATCH.
JAY McKEOWN'S GOT A PRETTY GOOD
ARM HERE.
SORT OF A JOHNNY UNITAS DROP
BACK.
THAT ONE IS OVER THE TOP.
McKEOWN WAS A STAR QUARTERBACK
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
HE STILL HAS THE ARM,
BUT THE PLAYMAKER'S STILL GOT
THE GREAT HANDS.
TWENTY SECONDS.
JAY IS RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
JAY McKEOWN, STILL WORKING
MICHAEL IRVIN.
CLIMBING THE LADDER TO GET
THAT ONE.
TEN SECONDS.
THAT ONE RIGHT IN BETWEEN
THE TWO 8s.
OH, AND HE GETS IT IN RIGHT
BEFORE THE HORN!
BOUNCING ONE THROUGH THE "H,"
PAST THE PLAYMAKER ON THE VERY
LAST SECOND OF THE SECOND EVENT
IN OVERTIME.
SO JAY FINISHES IN 59 SECONDS.
THAT GIVES HIM A TOTAL TIME
OF 1:38, SO AFTER TWO OVERTIME
EVENTS, JAY McKEOWN LEADS
AARON McKEEVER BY 13 SECONDS.
>> WELCOME B
TO "PROS VS. JOES."
WE'RE MIDWAY THROUGH OVERTIME,
AND JAY McKEOWN IS LEADING
AARON McKEEVER BY 13 SECONDS.
FOR OUR THIRD O.T. EVENT,
WE'RE TURNING THE TABLES HERE.
JOSE CANSECO, WHO HAS DONE
SOME PITCHING IN THE PAST, WILL
TAKE THE MOUND.
THE JOES MUST GET A HIT OFF JOSE
AND RUN AROUND THE BASES
IN ONE MINUTE.
>> I SHOULD THROW YOU
MY FASTBALL.
YOU WON'T HIT IT.
>> AARON McKEEVER STEPPING
INTO THE BOX.
>> STRIKE!
>> JOSE LOBS A NASTY KNUCKLEBALL
IN THERE FOR A STRIKE.
PLENTY OF MOMENTUM ON THAT ONE.
EVERYBODY REMEMBERS JOSE'S
INFAMOUS PITCHING DEBUT WITH
THE TEXAS RANGERS.
THROWING FROM THE STRETCH,
THE WIND-UP, AND HERE'S
THE SECOND PITCH.
THERE'S THE SWING AND THAT IS
A HIT.
AARON McKEEVER COMING THROUGH
ON THE SECOND PITCH WITH
A BEAUTIFUL HIT RIGHT INTO
CENTER FIELD AGAINST JOSE
CANSECO, AND HE'S TAKING OFF
AROUND THE BASES.
WHEN HE HITS HOME PLATE,
HIS CLOCK WILL STOP.
COME ON, AARON!
OOH, SLIDES HOME!
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> WHAT A NICE PERFORMANCE
BY AARON McKEEVER!
28 SECONDS IS YOUR TIME...
>> WHOO!
>> SO NOW YOUR CUMULATIVE TIME
IS 2:19.
>> HA HA HA!
I'M GONNA HAVE TO TURN IT UP
A LITTLE BIT.
>> NOW HERE'S JAY McKEOWN,
FACING JOSE CANSECO.
HERE'S THE WIND-UP.
FIRST PITCH ON THE WAY.
>> STRIKE!
>> AND THAT'S A STRIKE!
JAY LET THAT ONE GO RIGHT BY.
YOU GOT TO SWING TO GET A HIT!
HERE COMES THE SECOND PITCH.
OH, THAT IS WELL-HIT
BY JAY McKEOWN!
TAKES IT TO CENTER FIELD!
JOSE'S GETTING KNOCKED AROUND
OUT THERE BY THESE JOES!
JAY McKEOWN, ROUNDING THIRD.
COME ON, JAY!
>> SLIDE!
>> OH, WITH THE HEAD-FIRST
PETE ROSE-STYLE SLIDE!
HA HA HA!
>> WHOO!
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
BABY!
WHOO!
>> AND JAY FINISHES IN 23
SECONDS.
THAT GIVES HIM A TOTAL TIME
OF 2:01, SO AFTER 3 EVENTS
IN OVERTIME, JAY LEADS AARON
BY 18 SECONDS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY.
IT'S GETTING DOWN TO NAIL-BITING
TIME.
WE ARE DOWN TO OUR FINAL EVENT
IN OVERTIME.
IT'S BEEN A LONG JOURNEURNENEY, IT'
IT'S BEEN A LONG JOURNEURNENEY, ITS
BEEN A LONG EVENING, AND YOU
GUYS HAVE DONE GREAT.
BUT, AARON McKEEVER, YOU WERE
DOWN 18 SECONDS TO MY GUY
JAY McKEOWN, ALL RIGHT?
AND IT'S NOT GONNA END EASY.
YOU GUYS ARE IN THE CIRCLE,
12 FEET, VS. RANDY COUTURE.
YOU'VE GOT TO PUSH HIM OUT
OF THAT CIRCLE.
SOME PART OF HIS BODY HAS
TO TOUCH THE OUTSIDE MAT,
AND YOU GOT TO GET IT DONE
IN ONE MINUTE.
NOW, ONCE YOU PUSH HIM OUT
OR MAX OUT AFTER A MINUTE,
YOU HAVE GOT TO SPRINT--I MEAN,
RUN FOR YOUR LIFE--THROUGH
THESE TWO POLES.
THEN YOUR TIME WILL STOP,
AND WE WILL TELL YOU WHO WON
THE COMPETITION.
AARON, THIS IS YOUR LAST SHOT.
YOU CAN BE THE COMEBACK KID.
YOU'RE DOWN 18 SECONDS.
YOU'RE GOING FIRST.
GET IN THERE AND SEE
RANDY COUTURE.
>> WELL, THEY USUALLY SAVE
THE BEST FOR LAST, BUT HERE,
THEY SAVED THE WORST FOR LAST.
LONG WALK.
>> THAT IS A LONG WALK.
>> LOOK AT THAT MONSTER WAITING
ON YOU.
>> BREAK!
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
AARON McKEEVER, TRYING TO PULL
RANDY COUTURE OUT.
>> OUT, OUT, OUT!
>> AND RANDY'S ELBOW HIT
THE MAT!
>> OH, THEY SAID HE GOT HIM!
>> IT'S McKEEVER.
>> HE'S MOVING.
OH!
>> AARON McKEEVER,
UNBELIEVABLE PERFORMANCE!
COMING BACK AND TAKING OUT
RANDY COUTURE IN 12 SECONDS.
THAT IS A TOTAL TIME OF 2:31.
AARON HAS PUT INCREDIBLE
PRESSURE ON JAY.
HE NEEDS TO SOMEHOW GET RANDY
OUTSIDE OF THAT RING AND THEN
RUN THROUGH THE POLES IN LESS
THAN 30 SECONDS TO COME AWAY
WITH THE VICTORY HERE
IN OVERTIME.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT THEY'RE
SQUARING OFF.
>> BREAK!
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
JAY TAKES THE JERSEY OFF,
AND HE'S PUSHING COUTURE OUT.
COUTURE PUSHED HIM OUT AGAIN.
YOU GOT TO GET BACK IN THERE.
JAY TRYING TO BULL-RUSH HIM
AGAIN.
>> OUT, OUT, OUT!
>> AND HE'S GOT HIM OUT!
JAY McKEOWN'S GOT HIM OUT!
JAY McKEOWN IS A CHILD
OF DESTINY!
JAY McKEOWN COMING THROUGH